Backpack, yeah. Keys, walkie-talkie.
백팩, 네. 열쇠, 무전기.
Do I have everything?
나는 모든 것을 갖고 있나요?
Mike! We're outside! Over!
마이크! 우리는 밖에 있어요! 끝났습니다!
-Mike! - Yes! Coming! Over and out!
-마이크! - 네! 오는! 오버 앤 아웃!
- We're the kids in America - Whoa-oh
- 우리는 미국의 아이들입니다 - 와-오
Hey, what about breakfast?
아, 아침 식사는 어때요?
No, thanks! No time! Bye!
아니요, 고마워요! 시간이 없어! 안녕!
Hey! Watch it!
안녕하세요! 조심해!
- Nancy, straight home from school today. - Okay.
- 낸시, 오늘 학교에서 곧장 집으로 오세요. - 좋아요.
Mike, aren't you forgetting something?
마이크, 뭔가 잊어버린 게 있지 않나요?
Um, love you?
음, 사랑해요?
Oh, right! Thanks, Mom!
아, 그렇죠! 고마워요, 엄마!
- Here he comes. - Finally!
- 여기 그가 온다. - 마지막으로!
Let's go! We're gonna be late!
가자! 우리 늦을 거야!
Mike, relax. We're not gonna be late.
마이크, 진정하세요. 우리는 늦지 않을 거예요.
Yeah, we haven't been late once in the last five weeks.
그래, 우리는 한 번도 늦지 않았어 지난 5주 동안.
I know, but if we are...
알아요. 하지만 만약 그렇다면...
Just come on!
그냥 어서!
Come on!
어서 해봐요!
Almost there. Almost there.
거의 다 왔습니다. 거의 다 왔습니다.
Ugh! Move it, you bug blaster!
윽! 움직여라, 이 버그 블래스터야!
Dustin! Dustin, come in! Over!
더스틴! 더스틴, 들어오세요! 끝났습니다!
Come on, Dustin! We know you're there!
어서, 더스틴! 우리는 당신이 거기 있다는 것을 알고 있습니다!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no! Not now! Not now!
안 돼, 안 돼, 안 돼, 안 돼, 안 돼, 안 돼! 지금은 안돼! 지금은 안돼!
Dustin!
더스틴!
You know you have terrible timing.
당신은 타이밍이 좋지 않다는 것을 알고 있습니다.
We're heading directly to Will's. Meet us on Cornwallis. Over!
우리는 바로 Will's로 향하고 있습니다. 콘월리스에서 만나보세요. 끝났습니다!
- Wait for me! I'm at the mart! - Dustin!
- 기다려요! 나 마트에 있어! - 더스틴!
Fine. Meet you there. Over and out.
괜찮은. 거기서 만나요. 오버 앤 아웃.
Thanks, Dan. Gotta run!
고마워요, 댄. 달려야 해!
Wait, wait, wait. You're a dollar short again.
잠깐, 잠깐, 잠깐. 또 1달러가 부족하네요.
Sorry! I'll get you next time! You know I'm good for it!
죄송합니다! 다음에 꼭 데리러 갈게요! 내가 좋은 거 알잖아!
That's what you said about the cheese balls, and Pudding Pops,
그게 당신이 말한 것입니다 치즈볼과 푸딩팝에 대해
and whatever other abominations you children put in your gullets.
그리고 다른 가증한 것들도 너희 자녀들은 식도에 넣어라.
There's a new wave coming, I warn you
새로운 물결이 다가오고 있습니다. 경고합니다
- We're the kids in America - Whoa-oh!
- 우리는 미국의 아이들입니다 - 우와!
Found it!
찾았어요!
Everybody live for the music-go-round
모두가 음악을 즐기며 살아요
- Hey! Slow down, bud. - Sorry.
- 여기요! 천천히 하세요, 친구. - 죄송합니다.
Here's that mix you asked for. Finished last night.
요청하신 믹스가 여기 있습니다. 어젯밤에 끝났어요.
Maybe now you'll listen to more than just The Clash.
어쩌면 지금 당신은 듣게 될 것입니다 The Clash 그 이상입니다.
Thanks. I gotta go. The guys are waiting.
감사해요. 난 가야 해. 사람들이 기다리고 있습니다.
Mom said call if you're gonna be--
엄마가 그러실 거면 전화하라고 하셨는데--
Late!
늦은!
Jeez! Kid, are you okay?
이런! 꼬마야, 괜찮아?
Yes, yes, yes! I let it get late!
예, 예, 예! 늦도록 놔두었어요!
You know you don't actually go to school, right?
알잖아 너 사실 학교 안 가잖아, 그렇지?
So, I know you know, but I...
그래서, 당신도 알고 있다는 걸 알지만, 저는...
I need you to remember the ground rules, okay?
당신이 기억해줬으면 좋겠어 기본 규칙은 맞죠?
No attracting attention. Be careful who you talk to.
관심을 끌지 않습니다. 누구와 이야기하는지 조심하세요.
And we keep the cabin secret.
그리고 우리는 객실을 비밀로 유지합니다.
The last thing we need are strangers sticking their noses in around here.
우리에게 마지막으로 필요한 것은 낯선 사람이다 이 근처에 코를 박고 있어요.
I know the rules.
나는 규칙을 알고 있습니다.
Yeah, I know, but we can't have anyone finding out about your powers!
응, 알아, 하지만 우리는 그럴 수 없어 당신의 능력에 대해 알아내는 사람!
You see, that's what I'm talking about.
알다시피, 그것이 내가 말하는 것입니다.
I did it inside. No one can see.
내부에서 했어요. 아무도 볼 수 없습니다.
Look, kid, I'm just worried is all.
이봐, 꼬마야, 난 단지 걱정이 전부일 뿐이야.
- We're a family now. - I know!
- 이제 우리는 가족이에요. - 알아요!
Bottom line is I'd like to keep it that way.
결론은 나는 그것을 그대로 유지하고 싶습니다.
Me too.
저도요.
Mike.
마이크.
- Hey.
- 여기요.
- Hey! - Coat! I need a coat!
- 여기요! - 코트! 코트가 필요해요!
Anything happens to her,
그녀에게 무슨 일이라도 생기면
anything...
무엇이든...
These woods hide a lot of mistakes.
이 숲에는 많은 실수가 숨겨져 있습니다.
I... I got you something.
나... 내가 줄게 있어.
Why?
왜?
'Cause cops like doughnuts?
왜냐면 경찰은 도넛을 좋아하거든요?
Joke's on you, pal. Everyone likes doughnuts.
농담이에요, 친구. 다들 도넛을 좋아해요.
- Ready! - Be careful out there!
- 준비가 된! - 밖에선 조심하세요!
Yeah!
응!
Aw, sh... irt.
아, 셔츠... 젠장.
Couldn't have waited five seconds.
5초도 기다리지 못했을 겁니다.
Crud!
크루드!
Whoa! Slow down there, Henderson.
와! 천천히 하세요, 헨더슨.
Where you going in such a hurry?
그렇게 서둘러 어디로 가는 거야?
School. I'm gonna be late.
학교. 늦을 것 같아요.
Hey!
여기요!
We just want to see what you have for us in that book bag of yours.
우리는 단지 당신이 우리를 위해 무엇을 갖고 있는지 보고 싶을 뿐이에요 네 책가방 안에.
Books, brainiac. Wanna guess what's in my pencil case?
책, 두뇌. 내 필통에 무엇이 들어 있는지 추측하고 싶나요?
Hey! Get back here!
여기요! 여기로 돌아가세요!
We're gonna get you, Henderson!
우리가 널 잡을 거야, 헨더슨!
- Come here, dork! - Let's get that scumbag!
- 이리 오세요, 멍청이! - 그 쓰레기를 잡자!
- We're gonna get ya! - Yeah! Let's get that nerd!
- 우리가 널 잡을 거야! - 응! 그 괴짜를 잡자!
Give it up, geek!
포기해, 괴짜!
What the...?
무슨...?
Ah!
아!
I got snow in my crack!
내 균열에 눈이 내렸다!
So long, suckers!
오랜만이야, 멍청아!
Charlie! Where'd you go, man? I lost the nerd!
백인! 어디 갔어? 나는 괴짜를 잃었다!
Charlie!
백인!
Charlie?
백인?
What the...?
무슨...?
No, no, no, no!
안돼, 안돼, 안돼, 안돼!
Let's go!
갑시다!
Yeah! Let's go!
응! 갑시다!
Yeah!
응!
You guys, spring break is gonna be awesome this year!
여러분, 봄방학 올해는 정말 멋질 거야!
We'll finally get to show El some of our other hangout spots!
드디어 엘을 보여주게 된다 다른 행아웃 장소도 있어요!
- Like the arcade. - Yeah, and the pizza place.
- 아케이드처럼요. - 네, 그리고 피자집도요.
They've got deep dish now!
이제 깊은 요리가 생겼어요!
Deep dish? Will I like deep dish?
깊은 요리? 나는 깊은 요리를 좋아할까요?
El, you're gonna love it! It's like pizza on pizza!
엘, 정말 좋아할 거예요! 피자에 피자 같은 느낌이에요!
And the grease gets all over your fingers, and you lick it off, and it's so good!
그리고 기름기가 손가락 전체에 묻어납니다. 핥아주면 정말 맛있어요!
"El, you're gonna love it!"
"엘, 정말 좋아할 거예요!"
I think it's cute.
귀여운 것 같아요.
Cute? I've been having to wake up 30 minutes ahead of my alarm
귀여운? 난 지금까지 잠에서 깨어나야만 했어 알람보다 30분 앞서
just to do this!
그냥 이걸 하려고!
All he talks about is El this, El that! Ugh!
그 사람이 말하는 건 El 이것뿐입니다. 엘 그거! 윽!
Okay, we get it.
알았어, 알겠어.
You should be taking notes, Romeo.
메모를 해야 해, 로미오.
What? What did I say?
무엇? 내가 뭐라고 말했나요?
If we play our cards right, maybe Hopper will let you come with us
우리가 카드를 올바르게 사용한다면, 아마도 Hopper가 당신이 우리와 함께 가도록 허락해 줄 것 같아요
to the Starcourt mall when it opens Memorial Day weekend!
스타코트 몰로 현충일 주말에 열리면!
- That would be the ultimate hangout spot! - I heard it's gonna have a gaming store!
- 그곳이 최고의 수다방이 될 거예요! - 게임 가게가 생길 거라고 들었어!
Big whoop.
큰 웁.
What this town really needs is a Sam Goody.
이 마을에 정말 필요한 것 샘 구디입니다.
You can keep your music.
음악을 보관할 수 있습니다.
I'll take a Hot Dog on a Stick, Ground Round--
나는 막대기에 핫도그를 먹을 게요 지상 라운드--
You forgot Orange Julius, you jerks!
오렌지 율리우스를 잊어버렸구나, 이 멍청아!
What the hell happened to you?
대체 무슨 일이 일어난 거야?
Dirtbag Charlie and Noogie Jeff happened. That's what.
Dirtbag Charlie와 Noogie Jeff가 일어났습니다. 그게 다야.
Thanks for waiting for me, guys.
기다려줘서 고마워요 여러분.
Well, your mouth still works. Any internal bleeding?
글쎄요, 당신 입은 여전히 ​​작동하고 있어요. 내부출혈은 없나요?
No. But I escaped Mirkwood by the skin of my teeth.
아니요. 하지만 저는 Mirkwood에서 탈출했습니다. 내 치아의 피부로.
Looks like you brought some yellow snow with you too.
가져오신 것 같네요 너도 노란 눈이 좀 왔으면 좋겠어.
Har, har.
하, 하르.
Real funny.
정말 재밌어요.
Snow in your pants!
바지에 눈이 왔어요!
Get out of the road!
길에서 나가세요!
Stupid kids.
어리석은 아이들.
What? What do you mean you don't have your homework?
무엇? 무슨 뜻이야? 너 숙제 없어?
- Later, El! - See ya!
- 나중에, 엘! - 나중에 봐요!
- Bye, El! - Bye!
- 안녕, 엘! - 안녕!
- I wish I could go with you. - One day, you will.
- 같이 갈 수 있으면 좋겠어요. - 언젠가는 그럴 거예요.
You'll pick me up after school? 3-1-5?
학교 끝나고 데리러 올 거지? 3-1-5?
3:15. Yes.
3:15. 예.
Right. See ya!
오른쪽. 나중에 봐요!
Whoa. Whoa! Whoa!
와. 와! 와!
I can't wait to start D&D next week!
다음 주에 D&D를 시작하고 싶어요!
Me, too! And I figured out what module I want to use.
저도요! 그리고 난 알아냈어 내가 사용하고 싶은 모듈.
Actually, I had an idea.
사실, 나한테는 좋은 생각이 있었어요.
What--
뭐--
I'm so sorry. It was an accident.
정말 죄송해요. 그것은 사고였습니다.
You little jerk!
이 멍청아!
Ho ho!
호호!
You gonna let him get away with that?
그 사람이 그걸로 도망가게 놔둘 건가요?
What's it gonna be, Zombie Boy? Fat lip or black eye?
어떻게 될까요, 좀비 보이? 뚱뚱한 입술이나 검은 눈?
Hey, get off him! He said he was sorry.
이봐, 그 사람에게서 떨어져! 그는 미안하다고 말했다.
Back off! I'm busy here.
물러서세요! 나는 여기서 바빠요.
Hi. You're in front of my locker. Oops.
안녕. 당신은 내 사물함 앞에 있습니다. 이런.
Now you're in front of my locker.
이제 당신은 내 사물함 앞에 있습니다.
Hey, what's your problem? You some kind of freak?
이봐, 무슨 문제야? 당신은 일종의 괴물인가요?
Freak? Wow, that is so sweet of you to notice.
괴물? 와, 너 정말 다정해 알아 차리기.
You may also have noticed that you've worn out your welcome, sport.
여러분도 눈치채셨을 텐데요. 당신이 너무 지쳐서 환영합니다, 스포츠.
Whatever.
무엇이든.
Don't let the locker hit you on your way out.
라커가 당신을 때리게하지 마십시오 나가는 길에.
I'll catch you geeks later! Come on.
나중에 괴짜들을 잡아줄게! 어서 해봐요.
- Why didn't you do anything about it? - It's just a shirt.
- 왜 아무 조치도 취하지 않았나요? - 그냥 셔츠예요.
Will, you okay?
윌, 괜찮아?
Yeah, I'm fine.
응, 난 괜찮아.
Huh. Misfits. Nice.
뭐. 부적합. 멋진.
Um, thanks.
음, 고마워요.
Yeah, thanks for the help. There's a lot of meatheads in this school.
응, 도와줘서 고마워. 이 학교에는 멍청이들이 많아요.
Don't sweat it. Same jerk, different letterman jacket.
너무 걱정하지 마세요. 같은 바보, 다른 레터맨 재킷.
My theory is they clone them in every school.
내 이론은 그들은 모든 학교에서 그것들을 복제합니다.
I'm Mike. This is Will.
저는 마이크입니다. 윌이에요.
Sup? And, wait, what did he call you? Zombie Boy.
한모금? 그리고 잠깐만요, 그 사람이 당신을 뭐라고 불렀나요? 좀비 보이.
Wow. That is a new one. I'd stick with that if I were you.
우와. 그것은 새로운 것입니다. 내가 당신이라면 나는 그것을 고수할 것입니다.
Later.
나중에.
You guys okay?
너희들 괜찮아?
Yeah, thanks to that new kid.
응, 새로 온 애 덕분이야.
Who's her hairdresser? Mr. T?
그녀의 미용사는 누구입니까? T 씨?
She's punk. I like it.
그녀는 펑크입니다. 좋아요.
- Maybe you should try it, Lucas. - Oh, shut up.
- 한번 시도해 보시는 게 좋을 것 같아요, 루카스. - 아, 닥쳐.
Okay, people. Settle.
좋아요, 여러분. 해결하다.
Welcome back. New semester, new news to share with you all.
돌아온 것을 환영합니다. 새학기, 여러분 모두와 공유할 새로운 소식입니다.
I will be going on a sabbatical for the semester.
나는 안식년을 보낼 거야 학기 동안.
He's gonna become a priest?
그 사람이 신부가 될 거라고요?
What? No. It means he's going on, like, a work vacation.
무엇? 아니요. 그 뜻은 그 사람 지금 휴가 가는 중이거든요.
Oh, why didn't he just say so?
아, 왜 그 사람은 그렇게 말하지 않았지?
Ah!
아!
But I'm happy to report Hawkins Middle's newest teacher, Mrs. Baxter,
하지만 호킨스 미들(Hawkins Middle)의 소식을 전하게 되어 기쁘네요. 새로 온 선생님, Baxter 선생님,
will be your scientific sage while I'm away.
당신의 과학적 현자가 될 것입니다 내가 없는 동안.
Aw, man. What's gonna happen to AV Club?
아, 친구. AV 클럽에는 무슨 일이 일어날까요?
AV Club doesn't take a vacation, Mr. Clarke.
AV클럽은 휴가를 안가는데, 클라크 씨.
Sorry, boys. AV Club must endure without me for a few months.
미안해요, 얘들아. AV클럽은 견뎌야 한다 나 없이 몇 달간.
I've already briefed Mrs. Baxter, and I have complete confidence
나는 이미 백스터 부인에게 브리핑을 했습니다. 그리고 나는 완전한 자신감을 가지고 있어요
in her ability to mold your malleable minds.
그녀의 능력으로는 당신의 유연한 마음을 형성하기 위해.
I leave them in your hands.
나는 그들을 당신의 손에 맡깁니다.
Thank you, Mr. Clarke.
고마워요, 클라크 씨.
All righty, then.
그럼요.
Now, are you guys ready to learn about evolution?
자, 준비됐나요? 진화에 대해 배우려고?
Evolution is the process
진화는 과정이다
by which an organism adapts into an enhanced version of itself.
유기체가 적응하는 과정 그 자체로 향상된 버전이 됩니다.
Now, this process occurs over a vast stretch of time.
이제 이런 과정이 발생합니다 오랜 시간에 걸쳐.
But sometimes, it can leap forward.
그러나 때로는 앞으로 도약할 수도 있습니다.
Well, how about you talk amongst yourselves while I find the roster?
그럼, 둘이서 얘기하는 건 어때? 내가 명단을 찾는 동안 너희들은?
You could say I'm a little out of my element.
당신은 말할 수 있습니다 나는 내 요소에서 조금 벗어났습니다.
Oh my...
이런...
No? Okay.
아니요? 좋아요.
Okay. The big snowstorm is coming next week.
좋아요. 큰 눈보라 다음주에 옵니다.
We'll be on lockdown for a couple of days. That's when we'll start the campaign.
우리는 며칠 동안 폐쇄될 예정입니다. 그때부터 캠페인을 시작하겠습니다.
But first, we're gonna need extra cash since Eleven and Max are gonna play.
하지만 먼저 추가 현금이 필요해요 일레븐이랑 맥스가 놀 거니까.
Huh?
뭐?
Slow your roll, Lucas.
천천히 굴러가세요, 루카스.
I'm only gracing you with my presence just this once.
나는 단지 내 존재만으로 당신을 축복할 뿐입니다. 이번 한 번만.
Mike's right. We need money for more maps, extra dice, and a new graph pad, and...
마이크 말이 맞아요. 지도를 더 만들려면 돈이 필요해요. 추가 주사위, 새 그래프 패드, 그리고...
Not to mention snacks and drinks, guys. Come on.
간식과 음료는 말할 것도 없고요. 어서 해봐요.
All right. So what are we looking at here?
괜찮은. 그럼 우리는 여기서 무엇을 보고 있는 걸까요?
This is just sad.
정말 슬프네요.
We're still gonna be short.
우리는 아직 부족할 거예요.
Where are we supposed to get more cash?
현금을 더 확보할 수 있는 곳은 어디입니까?
I still have some of my arcade stash at home.
아직 내 아케이드 보관함이 좀 남아있어 집에서.
I got ten bucks from Nana for Christmas.
나나한테 크리스마스 선물로 10달러를 받았어.
My piggy bank is low,
내 돼지 저금통이 부족해요
but I haven't checked my couch cushions yet.
하지만 난 확인하지 않았어 내 소파 쿠션은 아직.
Hey, guys. I got an idea. But we're gonna need El.
안녕, 얘들아. 아이디어가 생겼어요. 하지만 엘이 필요해요.
Are you sure this is gonna work?
이게 성공할 거라고 확신해요?
Are you kidding me? This is one of my best ideas yet.
농담하는 거야? 이것은 내 최고의 아이디어 중 하나입니다.
Rich People Avenue, where driveways are paved with white gold.
리치 피플 애비뉴, 진입로는 화이트 골드로 포장되어 있습니다.
With your help, El,
당신의 도움으로 엘,
we could probably clear about a house a minute.
아마 클리어할 수 있을 거야 1분에 한 집 정도요.
I still don't know if it's such a good idea.
난 아직도 모르겠어 정말 좋은 생각이라면.
- You sure you're okay with this, El? - Friends help friends.
- 정말로 괜찮겠어요, 엘? - 친구는 친구를 도와줍니다.
Time to work my magic.
내 마법을 부릴 시간이야.
Hello, young lady. Is your mother home?
안녕하세요, 아가씨. 어머니는 집에 계시나요?
Well, aren't you just adorable?
글쎄, 당신은 정말 사랑스럽지 않나요?
I see that your driveway needs some snow removal.
네 집 진입로에 필요한 게 있는 것 같아 약간의 제설.
Well, I could use someone to clear it while I watch my stories.
글쎄, 누군가를 써서 그걸 정리할 수도 있겠지 내 이야기를 보는 동안.
For the low price of only five dollars,
단 5달러라는 저렴한 가격으로
this adorable face will plow your entire driveway.
이 사랑스러운 얼굴은 쟁기질할 것이다 당신의 진입로 전체.
And throw in the porch for free.
그리고 현관에 무료로 던져보세요.
Well, I usually wait for Mr. Plow, but I just can't resist those dimples.
글쎄요, 저는 보통 Mr. Plow를 기다립니다. 하지만 난 그 보조개를 참을 수가 없어.
Wonderful. You go in and watch your stories,
아주 멋진. 너는 들어가라 당신의 이야기를 들어보세요
and my dimples and I will take care of everything. Okay?
내 보조개와 내가 돌볼게 모든 것. 좋아요?
Bye-bye.
안녕.
All clear!
공습 경보 신호!
Anything happens to her,
그녀에게 무슨 일이 일어나든
anything...
무엇이든...
These woods hide a lot of mistakes.
이 숲에는 많은 실수가 숨겨져 있습니다.
Wait! Wait, wait, wait. I don't think we should do this.
기다리다! 잠깐, 잠깐, 잠깐. 내 생각엔 우리가 이렇게 하면 안 될 것 같아.
It'll be fine. We're keeping a lookout. No one will see.
괜찮을 거예요. 우리는 경계를 유지하고 있습니다. 아무도 볼 수 없습니다.
No, no, no. You don't understand. Hopper will kill me,
아니, 아니, 아니. 당신은 이해하지 못합니다. 호퍼가 날 죽일 ​​거야
literally kill me, if something happens to El.
말 그대로 나를 죽여라 만약 엘에게 무슨 일이 생긴다면.
Mike, it will be okay.
마이크, 괜찮을 거예요.
You just got some freedom. If something goes wrong,
방금 자유를 얻었습니다. 문제가 발생하면
no spring break hangouts, no more having fun, no more anything.
봄 방학 수다방이 없습니다. 더 이상 재미도 없고, 더 이상 아무것도 없습니다.
Party pooper!
파티 푸퍼!
You're dead, Henderson.
넌 죽었어, 헨더슨.
Snowball fight!
눈싸움!
- Whoa! - Take this!
- 와! - 이것을 받아라!
Coming at you!
당신에게 온다!
Get him, El!
그를 잡아, 엘!
There you go!
됐어요!
Oh man, it's old man Plow. He's gonna ruin everything.
아, 쟁기 노인이구나. 그는 모든 것을 망칠 것입니다.
Oh, sorry.
아, 미안해요.
What do you think you're doing?
지금 뭐하고 있는 것 같나요?
Now, I got work I gotta do around here, so you kids better get.
이제 여기서 해야 할 일이 있어서 그러니까 너희들은 얻는 게 좋을 거야.
Man, we were here first.
아저씨, 우리가 먼저 왔었어요.
First?
첫 번째?
This ain't no game.
이건 게임이 아닙니다.
But we have a right to be here, too.
하지만 우리에게도 여기에 있을 권리가 있습니다.
Rights? You snot-nosed rats ain't got no rights.
진상? 코딱지 쥐새끼들아 권리가 없습니다.
Now, you listen, and you listen good.
이제 당신은 듣고, 잘 듣습니다.
This here is your last warning. Before I take this shovel and I shove--
이것이 마지막 경고입니다. 이 삽을 들고 밀기 전에--
Mister!
아저씨!
Help me!
도와주세요!
Ah!
아!
- Help! - Whoa!
- 돕다! - 와!
Run!
달리다!
Look out, Lucas!
조심해, 루카스!
Help me!
도와주세요!
What was that?
그게 뭐였지?
Is it gone?
없어졌나요?
Not gone!
안 갔어!
Ah!
아!
- I'm slipping! - Hold on!
- 미끄러지고 있어요! - 기다리다!
Be right back!
곧 돌아오세요!
Wait, what? Where are you--
잠깐, 뭐? 당신은 어디에--
Whoa!
와!
It's back!
돌아왔다!
Oh, crud.
아, 크루드.
- Dustin!
- 더스틴!
Guys!
얘들아!
Dustin, catch this!
더스틴, 이거 잡아!
Ouch! Not helping!
아야! 도움이 안 돼요!
Guys!
얘들아!
Gross!
역겨운!
Help me!
도와주세요!
Dustin!
더스틴!
Dustin, are you okay?
더스틴, 괜찮아?
No! What the heck was that thing?
아니요! 그게 도대체 뭐였지?
It moved like some kind of shark.
그것은 마치 상어처럼 움직였습니다.
Snow sharks don't exist!
눈상어는 존재하지 않습니다!
Guys, you know exactly what that was.
여러분, 그것이 무엇인지 정확히 아실 ​​것입니다.
No, it can't be! El closed the gate to the Upside Down, right?
아니, 그럴 리가 없어! 엘이 문을 닫았어 거꾸로 하는 거죠, 그렇죠?
We need to call Hopper.
호퍼에게 전화해야 해요.
We don't have time to go to Hopper.
호퍼에게 갈 시간이 없어요.
We have to get that thing before it eats someone else.
우리는 그걸 얻어야 해요 다른 사람 잡아먹기 전에
Mike's right. If we don't stop it, the government could come back.
마이크 말이 맞아요. 우리가 그것을 멈추지 않는다면, 정부가 돌아올 수도 있다.
Maybe blame El and take her away.
어쩌면 엘을 비난하고 그녀를 데려갈 수도 있습니다.
It's settled. We catch it ourselves.
해결됐어요. 우리는 그것을 스스로 잡습니다.
Not settled. No one is asking El what she thinks we should do.
해결되지 않았습니다. 아무도 엘에게 묻지 않아 그녀는 우리가 무엇을 해야 한다고 생각하는지.
El?
엘자?
Catch it.
잡아라.
Stop it.
그만해요.
Just us.
바로 우리입니다.
No going back.
돌아갈 수 없습니다.
I hope this works, Mike.
이게 효과가 있었으면 좋겠어, 마이크.
Don't worry. This plan's gonna work.
괜찮아요. 이 계획은 성공할 거예요.
Then we'll get back to doing all the fun things we talked about. Okay?
그럼 다시 작업으로 돌아가겠습니다 우리가 이야기했던 모든 재미있는 것들. 좋아요?
Promise?
약속하다?
Promise.
약속하다.
Okay, guys. Confirm location.
알았어, 얘들아. 위치를 확인하세요.
El and Mike. Arcade rooftop. Lookout duty. Over.
엘과 마이크. 아케이드 옥상. 감시 임무. 위에.
Lucas and Max. West side bushes. Capture duty. Over.
루카스와 맥스. 서쪽 덤불. 포획 임무. 위에.
Will. East side arcade corner. Attack duty. Over.
할 것이다. 동쪽 아케이드 코너. 공격 임무. 위에.
Dustin. Parking lot. Bait. Pretty cheesed about it. Over.
더스틴. 주차장. 미끼. 그것에 대해 꽤 치즈가 있습니다. 위에.
Dustin, will you please stay in the kill zone? You keep moving around.
더스틴, 머물러 주시겠어요? 킬존에? 계속 돌아다닙니다.
I'm nervous, okay?
긴장돼요, 그렇죠?
And can we please come up with a better name than kill zone?
그리고 우리 좀 올라와도 될까요? 킬존보다 더 좋은 이름이 있나요?
Dustin, just stay where you are. Lucas, stop calling it kill zone.
더스틴, 그냥 그 자리에 있어주세요. 루카스, 킬존이라고 부르지 마세요.
Mike, I feel so stupid. I look like a meat-covered wind chime.
마이크, 나 정말 바보 같아. 나는 고기로 뒤덮인 풍경처럼 보입니다.
How do we even know this thing likes Slim Jims?
우리는 어떻게 알 수 있나요? 이게 Slim Jims를 좋아하는 걸까요?
We can't take a chance.
우리는 기회를 잡을 수 없습니다.
We need to sweeten the pot to get it out in the open.
우리는 냄비를 달게 해야 해 공개적으로 꺼내려고요.
Besides, the Slim Jims were Lucas's idea. Over.
게다가 Slim Jims는 Lucas의 아이디어였습니다. 위에.
Hey, you want to catch this thing or not?
이봐, 이거 잡을까 말까?
And who doesn't like Slim Jims?
Slim Jims를 좋아하지 않는 사람이 누가 있을까요?
Plus, it's better than Will's idea of covering you in fish.
게다가 윌의 생각보다 낫네요 당신을 물고기로 덮는 것입니다.
But sharks like fish.
하지만 상어는 물고기를 좋아해요.
I don't think we're hidden enough. These bushes are kind of measly.
나는 우리가 충분히 숨겨져 있다고 생각하지 않습니다. 이 덤불은 좀 심술궂습니다.
You sure that net isn't gonna be too heavy for you?
당신은 확실히 그 그물 너한테는 너무 무겁지 않을까?
Dude, my arms are literally stronger than yours.
야, 내 팔이 말 그대로 더 강해졌어 당신보다.
Oh no, the new kid.
아 안돼, 새로 온 애야.
Guys, code red! It's the creature. It's not taking our bait.
여러분, 코드 레드! 그것은 생물입니다. 우리의 미끼를 물고 있는 것이 아닙니다.
It's out to get the new kid. Go!
새로운 아이를 구하러 나갔습니다. 가다!
Get out of the snow! Run!
눈에서 벗어나세요! 달리다!
- Run, new kid! - Run!
- 달려라, 신입아! - 달리다!
- Get out of the snow!
- 눈에서 벗어나세요!
- What?
- 무엇?
Get out of the snow!
눈에서 벗어나세요!
- Get out of the snow!
- 눈에서 벗어나세요!
What the heck?
도대체 뭐야?
- Run! - Get out of the snow!
- 달리다! - 눈에서 벗어나세요!
What is going on?
무슨 일이야?